LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
I'm a soldier - that means I'm
Both a defendant and the judge
I am standing on both ends of the flame
Rounding curves
Overtaking life and death,
I run and fight with false shadows
No matter how many threads of
deception are woven together,
The truth shall illuminate
the face of light
Save your tears for the day
When our pain is far behind
On your feet, come with me
We are soldiers stand or die
Save your fears, take your place
Save them for the judgement day
Fast and free, follow me
Time to make the sacrifice.
We rise or fall
Don't you think you're overestimating
that PKF-spec cybernetic body?
It's long past its expiration date.
It's of no advantage.
Despite that, you still think you'll win?
That pisses me off.
Rout
The only way to knock out a cybernetic
body with its pain receptors shut off
is to cause trauma to the brain.
Bastard!
Are you an ex-Ranger?
So what if I am?
You're good.
The only reason I won must be due to
a small difference in our motives.
I have something I still have to do.
Don't follow me.
Dammit!
You know where he went?
Yeah.
Watch out!
Bastard...!
He's a remote control corpse!
Moron!
Are you trying to kill me, too?!
Don't worry.
With improvements in firing control software,
I have pinpoint accuracy that's
better than yours, Saitou-San.
Damn.
What's going on?
When was this guy's frontal lobe burned out?
He stinks.
Besides, even though it's obvious
that he's a remote control corpse,
how the hell are the signals
reaching all the way down here?
Maybe they used that?
Over there.
Batou!
What's up with their movements?
Are they both unmanned?
Batou!!!
Where's Batou?
He went after Kuze.
We're going after them!
Why were the armour suits here?
There's no reason that the
GSDF would intervene in this!
What about Coyle?
Saitou-San is after him.
Good.
Batou!
Batou-San!
What happened, Batou?
Sorry.
I let him get away.
You all right?
I'm fine.
I underestimated him.
Hurry up and go after him.
Bomer and the others will be along shortly.
Stay here.
Let's go!
Be careful.
He's good.
Hurry up and launch.
We'll have company soon.
He seems to have left the ship.
After you guys went to finish the
deal, he disappeared.
I see.
Kuze...
Cover me!
Major!
He's headed for Nagasaki!
We will recover Batou
and pursue them with the tilt-rotor!
Roger!
Sorry.
Batou-San!
Are you okay, Batou-San?
Forget about that; where's the Major?
The camouflaged ship left port.
We're going after them on the tilt-rotor.
Get Batou inside a Tachikoma.
It seems Coyle's frontal
lobe was fried a while ago.
He was probably already a remote control corpse
by the time Russian authorities
started tailing him.
In any case, by the time we arrived,
neither Jablov nor Kagazaki were here.
The armour suit pilot was
also a remote control corpse.
He was either a Sagawa employee or a local labourer.
The suit is also one that was
never delivered to the GSDF.
This deal has another side to it.
This might provide a clue as
to where Kuze got the money.
It looks like his source provided
an unbelievable sum of money.
All right.
That investigation will wait till later.
Let's hurry.
We'll have company soon enough.
Let's head towards Shikotan for now.
The same ship as ours should have
already departed from Dejima.
We'll wait till our people arrive.
then slip through the Coast Guard's net.
We'll be in trouble if those guys come from above.
I'll prep the anti-aircraft guns.
What's the situation?
They got you, Old Man?
I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
We'll depart immediately.
We're going after Kuze's ship.
Ishikawa, shake him off!
Ishikawa!
A suicide bomber!
Dammit!
Houeimaru
Lead...
They're not coming.
Seems he stopped them.
He?
Were the authorities aware of the deal?
Could've been.
But we got the plutonium.
That's right.
Now that we have this, Dejima will become our nation.
What's wrong?
Let's not get optimistic yet.
At least, not until we get it to Dejima.
True.
So, I have a suggestion.
What?
I will go to Dejima alone from here on.
You guys will get off the ship at Shikotan.
But the Coast Guard's patrol ships
will be showing up ahead of us.
How about we go by land, then?
We may be able to deceive the police.
No, that's impossible.
We can't enter Dejima by land.
We can only go by sea.
Besides, it's more effective to
slip past the Coast Guard's net
and bring in the plutonium in
order to declare independence.
We'll become a nuclear power
after our demonstration.
In the end, nuclear weapons are a deterrent.
They're not something we can use.
If that's the case,
then all the more reason for us to go too.
What're you going to do by yourself if
you get in a scuffle with the Coast Guard?
I can survive by myself
and I will bring the plutonium back.
But if you're with me, you'll be in the way.
Since you've been so blunt about it.
I guess we can only have faith in you.
Three million refugees are
watching me in real-time.
I can't go back now.
Is that a Hokkaido Police chopper?
It's almost like déjà vu.
If I remember right, didn't we see
something identical yesterday?
Chief,
Batou and Ishikawa's rescue
will be your first priority.
And as for the Coast Guard,
I'm sorry but you'll be dealing with it.
I'm going to take Pazu and
Bomer to investigate Sagawa--
there's something that bothers me.
Very well.
If the plutonium went to Kuze,
the Coast Guard is the last line of defence.
Maybe.
Several identical camouflaged ships
had already been built in Dejima.
Have them be careful.
Considering the distance,
I think it'll be a few days before he passes through
international waters and shows up on Nagasaki's coast, though.
Understood.
Sagawa Electronics
Hm?
Chief, were we planning on
having photographers over?
Hey, are you suffering from amnesia or something?
That's the girl who's going to
inherit the Uesawa Photo Studio;
we've been doing business
with them for forty years.
Refugees, huh.
This place is too mechanised.
Maybe they can't survive with
only specialised talents.
You guys hit up the information processing
room and the memory management room.
I'll go to the president's office.
If this deal was staged by the
Cabinet Intelligence Agency,
there is a high possibility that
the plutonium didn't go to Kuze.
I want to find proof of that.
Eighty to ninety percent of Gouda's
plans have already gone through,
but he plans to fabricate the "fact" that
the refugees became a nuclear power first,
to make the SDF deployment certain.
We will find something and go back.
Roger.
If this continues,
we'll have a civil war with the refugees,
and his plan to have the current regime
expand the military will succeed.
Still, how will you end the refugee problem, Gouda?
It must be Kagazaki.
It looks like this one was a temporary body,
He tried to switch to his main body and escape,
but got killed anyway,
These must be Jablov and his man.
Mechanising this place was their undoing.
Like Chlordane, they were killed
without anyone's knowledge.
Everything has been deleted.
Chlordane's data is now our only lead.
Pazu, Bomer, report.
Only records about the company are left here.
There are traces of massive
amounts of data that were deleted,
but recovery looks to be difficult.
Same here.
I see.
Judging from the situation, this deal seems to have
been under the Cabinet Intelligence Agency's control,
but there is no proof that the
Agency was controlling Coyle.
After we record data from this
site, we'll return to HQ.
Roger.
Gouda's still holding us
all in the palm of his hand.
What will you do, Kuze?
Don't worry.
It's just that it doesn't feel like a
part of me when it's only been three days.
How's the old man?
Fortunately, his brain functions are
showing no signs of abnormalities.
He'll be on his feet in a month or so.
We've sustained a lot of damage in this sortie.
We lost a man, with one more injured;
we also lost the tilt-rotor.
We can pretty much call it a total defeat.
Kuze's camouflaged ship hasn't shown itself yet?
It hasn't shown up on the Coast Guard's net yet.
The government hasn't made
any noticeable moves, either.
The refugees are lying low for now as well,
so the consensus is that there isn't
enough reason to deploy the SDF.
Though unofficially,
the Chinese government appears to be concerned
as to how to deal with the autonomous region.
Autonomous region?!
Considering that they wouldn't take in refugees.
what a selfish attitude.
The fact that Kayabuki is pro-China
may be what's emboldening
the Chinese side's remarks.
For now, only a select few in the Coast Guard
know that there may be plutonium
on the camouflaged ship,
but it seems Diet members, like
Kanzaki, have caught onto the situation
through their own information networks.
As a result,
we should consider it fact that there are many
within the ruling party who are aware of the situation.
I wonder if the reason that Chief Cabinet Secretary
Takakura hasn't done anything, despite the circumstances,
is because the obstacle to
SDF deployment will be removed
if plutonium is brought into Dejima,
in accordance with the Cabinet
Intelligence Agency's scenario.
Sounds about right.
It looks like there are places on the net
where they're starting to
yammer about the possibility
that there was a plutonium deal between
the Russian mafia and the refugees.
How will the refugees make their move?
If the plutonium didn't go to
Kuze, as the Major speculates,
what do you think Kuze will do?
He has been orchestrating the
situation with his rare charisma
and his ability to take action
and assess the situation.
but in the end, he's only one terrorist among many,
in terms of both strategy and force.
Gouda has the upper hand, with the state's backing.
As a result, Kuze's actions
follow Gouda's scenario,
and Kuze is playing a role that changes
the situation in the direction Gouda wants,
but it's not as though Kuze is
actually under Gouda's control.
If there is a factor that
may overturn the situation,
Kuze's actions may be it.
Strange how things are turning out,
but this may also be what the
Stand Alone Complex makes possible.
Chief, a report just came in
that a Coast Guard patrol ship
found a camouflaged ship
believed to have Kuze on board
off the shores of Nagasaki in Amakusanada.
Are they keeping us informed of the situation?
Yes, we have a live feed from the patrol ship.
Connect it to this monitor.
Roger.
The ship's not stopping.
Warning shots won't work.
Bring her closer to the ship.
Roger.
Bring her closer.
Prepare to fire on the ship.
Fire!
Did we hit her?
We did.
Affirmative, Sir.
They're shooting at us!
We're hit!
Starboard! We've taken damage to starboard!
We're being attacked.
Prepare to fire in self-defence.
Fire!
Fire, fire!
Watch it!
Avoid the fuel tank!
What if the plutonium blows up?!
Not good.
This footage will go to the media, too.
The ship seems to have a fire on deck.
Detain the ship's crew!
Bring her closer!
Get her closer and catch them.
Hey, what's going on?
Coast Guard
What is that?
Captain!
What?
Nagasaki is...!
Nagasaki?!
Hey...
The lights are going out.
What's going on?
The refugees triggered a massive
blackout with a terrorist attack?
To cover for Kuze, I guess.
It is difficult to believe that the refugees
would be able to accomplish that much.
Huh? Then...
At the end of the chain reaction of hate
is a drawn-out war with the refugees...
Finding out a galaxy
of planets and stars within me.
Listening to each of them
singing the same silent melody.
I've never seen such beauty
in possibility...
No smack of doubt or fear.
(Wake up)
I hear a voice.
(And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
I see inside
(the time is right)
see the light now ever holding me.
All the truth,
(All the truth)
All I need,
to make all this reality.
(it's inside)
The beauty within the shell.
(deep within the shell)
(within the shell)
(Wake up)
I hear a voice
(And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
(the time is now)
I see inside,
see the light now ever holding me.
All the truth,
(All the truth)
all I need,
to make all this reality,
it's inside
right here within the shell.